pain. Um
crisis precipitates change. People
telling ghost stories really really
scares me. I think I'm a victim. I think
you're a victim. Everybody is telling
weird ghost stories and we're getting
really high off of these ideas, but we
don't have any clue about the
consequence. We don't have, as in my
opinion, we do have the ability in
controlled context to trace the effects
of our word of our of our rhetoric. We
don't track exactly how these behaviors,
these influential ideas, these ghost
stories
change people's lives. Now, of course,
we can always say everybody's working as
hard as they can. They're evolutionarily
fit beings trying to make the most of
their situations. So, we have a bit of
bias, survivorship bias, of saying, "Oh,
we did fine with how this is. Why don't
we simply do what we know?"